(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-06-28T00:32:09.920104",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
Special guests are here to join the fun so don't blink
The moment we've all been waiting for...
こんなことになるならなんて
If things were going to turn out like this,
出会う前にわかってたら
if only I had known before we met...
もう少しだけしゃんとした僕を見せられたはずなんだ
I should have been able to show you a slightly more decent side of myself.
どうしたらいいのかなんて
What should I do?
頭ではわかってるけど
In my head, I know, but...
なにげないちょっとした言葉でわあ
A casual, small word of yours...
嬉しくなっちゃって
makes me so happy,
こんなバレバレじゃかっこ悪いな
being this obvious is so uncool.
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないな
But I can't back down like this.
でも今も顔が照れくさくて
Yet even now, my face is burning up...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないです
I can't say that I like you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you.
空回り空回り
Spinning my wheels, spinning my wheels,
何度も言えずつまずいた
fumbling to say it over and over.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないです
I like you so much, I can't help myself.
明日こそは言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕に同じように
If you felt the exact same way...
恋してたらなんて考えちゃうんだ
...about me, I keep imagining.
会えない日が続いてる
The days we can't meet keep going on.
このままじゃよろしくない
At this rate, it's not looking good.
会ったところで何ができるって
It's not like I can do much...
わけじゃないんだけど
...even if we actually met.
こんな恋は二度とないな
A love like this will never happen again.
頭ではわかってるけど
In my head, I know, but...
まぶしすぎるその笑顔がわあ
That smile of yours is just too bright...
僕を焦らせるんだ
...and it makes me panic.
ずっと見ていたくなるような
I want to keep looking at you forever,
目そらしたくなってしまうような
yet it makes me want to look away.
こんな気持ちはわかるのかな
I wonder if you understand this feeling.
あなたが笑ってくれるならそれでいいです
As long as you smile, that's enough for me.
でも隣は僕がいいな
But I wish I were the one by your side.
もしかしたら実はもう気付いてるんじゃないかな保存
What if you've actually already noticed?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないです
I like you so much, I can't help myself.
言えるかな
Could I say it?
手をひっくり返すくらいの
As easily as turning over my hand...
粋なセリフは
An elegant line like that,
言えそうにないな
I don't think I can say it.
どうしたってこの気持ちは
No matter what, this feeling
抑えられそうにはないんだ
Doesn't seem like it can be suppressed.
あなたと出会ったあの日から
From that day I met you,
ずっと気持ちは変わらない けど
My feelings haven't changed at all... but,
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say that I like you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
Will this feeling reach you?
こちとら頭は空回り
On my end, my head is spinning in circles,
何も言えずまたさよなら
I can't say anything and we say goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I like you so much that I can't stand it.
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to say it tomorrow, for sure.
あなたも僕と同じように
If only you, just like me,
恋してたらなんて考えてる
were in love... I wonder about that.
でも分かってる 考えすぎだってこと
But I know that I'm just overthinking things.
Kobo Kanaeru, at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hi everyone, konbanwa!
Hi everyone, good evening!
Kobo Kanaeru desu!
I'm Kobo Kanaeru!
Kobo no 3D seitan haishin e youkoso!
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D Birthday Stream...
2025! Pachi pachi pachi!
2025! Clap clap clap!
How was Kobo's performance?
Hmm? Dou datta?
How was it?
Mata guitar de detekita yo ne? Hehe!
I came out with my guitar again, didn't I? Hehe!
Eh, chotto matte.
Uh, wait a second.
Let me put the guitar down first.
Ah, yossho yossho yossho.
Okay, there we go.
Okay! Phew...
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
Kobo no 3D seitan haishin e youkoso!
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
This time,
I, Kobo, will be hosting an...
I, Kobo, will be hosting a...
idol-mitai concert...
concert like an idol's...
themed 3D Birthday Stream for about an hour!
With a lot of amazing and awesome guests!
I bet you guys can't wait!
Huh? Eh?
Kobo... oh?
Is there something different?
Ah, the chat! Nice!
Nice eyes, chat, you noticed it!
Yeah, you're right! Look at Kobo's new stage!
Wah!
Wow!
Dekai!
It's huge!
Atarashii stage ya!
A brand new stage!
There's a... a big cirrus right here!
Cirrus, oki na cirrus.
Cirrus... big cirrus clouds.
Unyu unyu, unyu unyu...
Squiggly, squiggly...
And so many stars! Stars! So many stars!
And then, a big... a big rainbow right here!
Big, very very big rainbow!
And so many clouds, because...
I don't know, I think it's just very aesthetic, yeah!
And the floor!
Floor! Floor mite!
The floor! Look at the floor!
Wa! Nanka pattern...
Wow! This pattern is like...
umi mitai. You know?
the ocean. You know?
Yeah, like my hair! Hehe!
So, um...
Don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay?
Especially later, okay? Get a lot of screenshots!
Okay?
And then post your comments, your moments, your impressions, your everything...
with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS!
Soshite, Kobo no 3D birthday haishin,
Also, for Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream,
SNS ni hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 o tsukete,
please post on SNS with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025,
comment ya omoide, kansou nado nado toukou shite ne!
with your comments, memories, impressions, and so on!
And... right!
Are you guys ready for the next performance?
Okay, let's go to the next performance!
Wait, I try... to remember...
Wait, I'm trying... to remember...
ラストのポーズ、エクスポジション...
For the last pose, exposition...
あ、おっけー。覚えています。
Ah, okay. I remember.
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？
Now everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべちゅーして
Special CHU for me...
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
とくべつちゅーして
Give me a special CHU.
いちばん大事がイイ
I want to be your number one.
キミが作るオリジナルの
Make it an original,
とくべつちゅーして
special CHU for me.
まぶしくて目が覚めて
Waking up to the dazzling light,
愛おしく思ってるよ
I think of how precious you are.
眠り姫のように
Like a sleeping beauty,
優しくくちづけて
gently kiss me.
夢めいたこの世界
In this dreamlike world,
夕暮れかかるキミがいる
there you are under the dusk.
全てに触れずに
Without touching anything else,
２人だけでいよう
let's just be the two of us.
私のこと 独占して
Monopolize me completely,
キミだけのものになってみてもいい
I wouldn't mind becoming yours alone.
なんでもある日の
Even on an ordinary day,
なんでもないに気づいてね
please notice the little things.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
キミのとくべつにして
Make me your special one.
ねぇもっと give me a kiss もっと 私は
Hey, give me more kisses, because I...
キミでいっぱいだよ
am already full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
An unbreakable ribbon knot,
小指キュって縛って
tightly tied around our pinky fingers.
そうよ一生一緒がいいの
That's right, I want to be together forever,
とくべつが欲しい
I want something special.
2人きり週末は
On weekends with just the two of us,
奏でてよハーモニー
play our harmony.
流れ星見たら
If you see a shooting star,
私を想ってほしい
I hope you think of me.
甘々なキミなのに
Even though you're so sweet,
広い街 吸い込まれ
being sucked into the wide city.
戦う姿に
To your fighting figure,
大きなハナマルだね
a big gold star for you.
好きなトコ 優しいトコ
The things I like, the gentle parts,
キライなトコも 優しいトコ
even the things I dislike, and the gentle parts.
誰にもあげない
I won't give them to anyone else,
私だけ一人占め
I'll keep you all to myself.
裏だって今までないコト
Even the hidden side is something new,
同じは要らないんです
I don't need the same old things.
ねぇもっと give me more love 私のため
Hey, give me more love, for my sake,
生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for me.
だからウサギと私は
So, like a rabbit, I...
寂しくさせないで
please don't let me get lonely.
それじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not really possessiveness,
苦しいのが好き
I just like the sweet pain.
ショートケーキ
Like the strawberry
イチゴみたいに座ってもいい？
on top of a shortcake, can I sit there?
赤く甘い恋だもん
It's a red, sweet love,
誰かが見上げた
someone looked up at it.
大好きも返してもらって
Please return my love in full,
全部私に
all of it to me.
ちょうだい
Give it to me,
もっと
more!
キミは神様が作る
You are a miracle
奇跡のような人
made by God.
つれた顔もその寝顔も
Whether your annoyed face or sleeping face,
守ってあげるね
I will protect them all.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" is not enough.
キミのとくべつにして
Make me your special one.
ねぇもっと give me a kiss もっと 私は
Hey, give me more kisses, because I...
キミでいっぱいだよ
am already full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
An unbreakable ribbon knot,
小指キュって縛って
tightly tied around our pinky fingers.
ねぇベイビー最初で最後の
Hey baby, make this the first and last...
とくべつにしてね
special moment for us.
うわああああ！
Wahhhhh!
てんてんてんてん天国 (feat. ななひら & PA組)
[Title: Tenten-Tenten Tengoku (feat. Nanahira & PA-gumi)]
てん てん てん
Ten, ten, ten...
てん てん てんてんてんてんてん
Ten, ten, ten-ten-ten-ten-ten...
ごこちごこちごこごこ
Heavenly feeling, feeling...
オープンセサミ！
Open Sesame!
闇と光の交わるプラクティカル
A practical mixture of darkness and light,
今宵味わうカテドラル
a cathedral to be savored tonight.
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
An dancing, intertwining zodiac,
恋の駆け引きのタイブレイク
a tiebreaker of love's tactics.
飾らない存在
An unpretentious existence,
ただ気を惹きたい
I just want to catch your eye.
夢見心地 触れ合い 惑わせたい
Dreamy, touching, I want to lead you astray,
曖昧に解けないココチ
my vague feelings won't melt.
それは甘い鮮やかな赤いアイ...
It is a sweet, vivid, red eye/love...
見つめて限界。
Staring until the limit.
月夜に誘われて...
Enticed by the moonlit night...
天使と悪魔と
An angel and a demon,
天使と悪魔が甘さ加勢した。
The angel and demon boosted the sweetness.
天国地獄の
Of heaven and hell,
狭間で出会った。
Met in the gap.
天使と悪魔と
An angel and a demon,
An angel and a demon...
悪魔が集って踊れば
If they gather and dance,
天国地獄の
Of heaven and hell...
天国地獄の門が開く。
The gates of heaven and hell open.
闇と光の交わるファナティック。
A fanatic crossing of darkness and light.
今宵味わうサイケデリック。
Savoring the psychedelic tonight.
踊り絡み合うゾディアック。
Dancin' and intertwining Zodiac.
恋の駆け引きのタイブレイカー。
The tiebreaker of love's tactics.
DEAD or ALIVE, DEAD or ALIVE,
DEAD DEAD DEAD, PASS PASS PASS.
DEAD DEAD DEAD, PASS PASS PASS, LET'S GO!
生けた魂をトレイに置いて。
Place the living soul on a tray.
巡る5枚のカード揺れる炎。
Five rotating cards, flickering flame.
先にあなたが提示したら...
If you present yours first...
もう迷わないグラス飲み干して。
No more hesitation, drain the glass.
こんなお遊戯、祈りないこの勝負。
Such a play, this match with no prayers.
今、天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開いていく。
Now, the gate connecting heaven and hell is opening.
天使と悪魔、死者と生者が入り乱れ...
Angels and demons, the dead and the living mingle...
踊り、笑い、すべては混沌の中に飲み込まれてゆく。
Dancing, laughing, everything is swallowed into chaos.
それは世界の終焉であり、新たなる始まりでもあったのだ。
It was the end of the world, and also a new beginning.
DEAD or ALIVE, DEAD or ALIVE,
DEAD DEAD DEAD, PASS PASS PASS.
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea-hea-hea-heaven, hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄！
hea-hea-heaven, hell!
天 天 天 天国 天
Hea-hea-hea-heaven, hea-
天 天 天 天国 地獄！
hea-hea-heaven, hell!
月夜に誘われて 天使と悪魔と
Enticed by the moonlit night, with an angel and a demon,
天使と悪魔と 天使と悪魔が
With an angel and a demon, the angel and demon...
甘さ加勢した 天国地獄の
Boosted the sweetness of heaven and hell.
恍惚消えない果てないムーンライト。
Unfading ecstasy, endless moonlight.
天国地獄の 天国地獄の
Between heaven and hell, heaven and hell,
狭間で出会った 天使と悪魔と
Met in the gap, with an angel and a demon,
天使と悪魔と 天使と悪魔が
With an angel and a demon, the angel and demon...
集って踊れば 天国地獄の
If they gather and dance, of heaven and hell,
天国地獄の 天国地獄の狭間で出会った。
Met in the gap between heaven and hell, heaven and hell.
天使と悪魔と 天使と悪魔と 天使と悪魔が
With an angel and a demon, with an angel and a demon, the angel and demon...
集って踊れば DEAD or ALIVE.
If they gather and dance, DEAD or ALIVE.
天国 DEAD or ALIVE 天国地獄。
Heaven, DEAD or ALIVE, Heaven and Hell.
DEAD or ALIVE 天国 DEAD or ALIVE 天国地獄！
DEAD or ALIVE, Heaven, DEAD or ALIVE, Heaven and Hell!
Iblis dari mana kamu?
What kind of demon are you?
Eh, iblis dari mana kamu? Waah, gatelnya orang iblis.
Eh, what kind of demon are you? Whoa, this demon is so cheeky.
Wahai!
Hey!
Itu empat tanduk, bahaya sekali!
Those four horns, they look super dangerous!
Iya, jadi gini...
Yeah, so it's like this...
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I came all this way...
Ya, jauh-jauh...
Yes, all this way...
Meskipun tidak diundang!
Even though I wasn't invited!
Oh, diundang!
Oh, you were invited!
Iya, kayaknya kamu mengundang yang lain deh tadi.
Yeah, but I think you invited others earlier.
Maksudnya... どういう意味？
You mean... What do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba 日本語？
Why the sudden Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Jepang ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter nggak? Pusing.
Can you stop spinning? I'm getting dizzy.
Pusing? Ya udah. Malaikat kok pusing, guys.
Dizzy? Fine. An angel getting dizzy, guys.
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya, pengen main bareng.
Actually, I came here just to tease you. I want to play together.
Pengen godain kamu aja. Sini, sini, sini!
I just want to tease you. Come here, come here!
Pulang kamu habis ini? Loh, kamu habis ini pulang sama aku kan?
Are you going home after this? Hey, you're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang?
Go home?
Iya, habis ini nggak ada apa-apa lagi kan?
Yeah, there's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain? Enak-enak aku di atas.
Why would I? It's nice up there for me.
Masa kamu mau seret gua?
Are you really going to drag me down?
Loh, kita... Loh bukannya kita...
Wait, we... Aren't we...
Kita, kita... Kamu aja iblis.
We, we? You're the only demon here.
Ajak dong, ajak dong Mbak.
Take me with you, sis.
Reine: Kamu, saya ajak? / Kobo: Aku kesepian.
Reine: I should take you? / Kobo: I'm lonely.
Ayo, sini, bareng. Fallen angel nih.
Come on, let's go together. Fallen angel here.
Ngak, nggak ada fallen angel. Nggak ada fallen angel ya, guys.
No, there's no fallen angel. No fallen angel, guys.
Mau saksikan nggak aku panah?
Want to witness me shooting the arrow?
Iya, iya, coba, coba, coba. Panah, sore!
Yeah, yeah, show me. Shoot, shoot!
Satu, dua, tiga, puh!
One, two, three, phew!
Iya, iya, gila gila gila.
Yeah, yeah, crazy crazy crazy.
How to tame your demon.
How to tame your demon. Jadi light novel.
How to tame your demon. It becomes a light novel.
Gimana tadi freestyle kita keren banget ya guys?
How was our freestyle just now? It was so cool, right guys?
Iya, lucu gak guys?
Yes, wasn't it cute, guys?
Atas...
Up...
Bawah...
Down...
Atas...
Up...
Bawah...
Down...
Atas...
Up...
Terus tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
But then, when you went up, I went down.
Kebalik.
Reversed.
Tahu ya, orang mah kebalik kiri kanan.
I know, right? Usually, people reverse left and right.
Dia kebalik letak atas.
But she reversed it upwards.
Atas...
Up...
Aku bawah.
I'm down.
Atas...
Up...
Kocak, kocak. Ya udah.
So funny. Okay then.
Ya udah.
Okay then.
Ya udah kalau gitu, aku, aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya...
Okay then, I'm actually a busy woman...
Jadi kayak memang nggak ada, nggak gitu banyak waktu.
So I don't really have that much time.
Aku di sini mampir...
I'm just dropping by...
Mampir dikit aja bentar.
Dropping by for just a bit.
Kasih tiga, kasih lima detik buat kamu.
Giving you three, five seconds.
Buset...
My goodness...
Buset, bumi milik ego-ku nih.
My goodness, "the earth belongs to my ego."
Asyik...
Cool...
Oke...
Okay...
Baik...
Alright...
Fiksi ya guys, ini cerita fiksi.
This is fiction, guys. This is a fictional story.
Jangan ditiru adik-adik.
Don't copy this, kids.
Fiksi, fiksi, fiksi ya guys.
Fiction, fiction, fiction, okay guys?
Sensitif ini sensitif.
This is sensitive, sensitive.
Fiksi, bohongan.
Fiction, a lie.
Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Nggak mau ikut aku lagi?
You don't want to join me anymore?
Bye!
Jagaiin ini anak ya guys!
Take care of this kid, guys!
Kita lihat perilakunya beneran seiso atau nggak, tuh lihat bajunya.
Let's see if she's really seiso or not, look at her clothes.
Jagaiin, jagaiin! Ya udah, bye!
Take care of her, take care of her! Okay then, bye!
Bye!
Bisa jadi fallen angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I could become a fallen angel because of her instigation, guys.
Nggak jelas.
Absurd.
なんとかしなくちゃならなくて
I had to do something,
突然メイドになっちゃって
suddenly turning into a maid.
いつものようにお店の掃除
Cleaning the shop as usual,
扉開いちゃって目が合った
the door opened and our eyes met.
なんだか忙しくなっちゃって
It became kind of busy,
あわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
and I became quite clumsy too.
お仕事中に！
During work!
推しに夢中に！
Crazy about my favorite!
どこを探しても見当たらないじゃん！
I can't find them anywhere!
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment.
もういいよ！
Ready!
秘密だよね？
It's a secret, right?
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen in love.
ねぇ、好きって言って！
Hey, say you love me!
ときどきキョン！送るラブビーム
Tokidoki Kyon! Sending a love beam,
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that makes you crazy about me?
ほら ときどきキョン！私大暴走
Look, Tokidoki Kyon! I'm running wild,
君も夢中にさせる恋の味
it's the taste of love that makes you crazy too.
もう君にキョン！私大暴走
Already Kyon for you! My big rampage,
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that lets me be crazy with you?
だから君がキョンってなる恋になって
So fall into a love that makes you go Kyon,
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
here, have one, this is the taste of love.
楽しくて仕方なくなっちゃって
It became so fun I couldn't help myself,
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
but soon it started coming to an end.
会いたくなって落ち込んじゃって
I wanted to see you and got depressed,
君とぶつかって目が合った
then I bumped into you and our eyes met.
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
I wanted to see you over and over again,
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
saying just today is not enough.
計画通り！
Just as planned!
私の勝利！
It's my victory!
君に会いたくて仕方がないよ
I want to see you so much I can't help it!
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment.
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
きみだけだよ
It's only you.
もうずっと
Always and forever,
愛し合いたいよね？
we want to love each other, right?
ねぇ、好きって言って！
Hey, say you love me!
ときどきキョン！君にラブビーム
Tokidoki Kyon! Sending a love beam to you,
ふたり夢中になれる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that makes us both crazy?
ほら ときどきキョン！私大恋愛
Look, Tokidoki Kyon! My big romance,
君も夢中にさせる恋の魔法
it's the magic of love that makes you crazy too.
もう君にキョン！私大興奮
Already Kyon for you! My big excitement,
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that lets me be crazy with you?
だから君がキョンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall into a love that makes you go Kyon,
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
here, have one, this is the taste of love.
もしも このままだとしたら
If things were to stay this way,
ここで会うこともなくなって
we might never even meet here again.
もう 君の声が
Already, your voice...
聞きたくなるの
I'm starting to want to hear it.
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment.
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
秘密なのに
Even though it's a secret.
もういいよ！
Ready!
このまま好きになっていく
I'm falling in love with you just like this.
好きって言って！
Say you love me!
ときどきキョン！送るラブビーム
Tokidoki Kyon! Sending a love beam,
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that makes you crazy about me?
ほら ときどきキョン！私大暴走
Look, Tokidoki Kyon! I'm running wild,
君も夢中にさせる恋 of 味
it's the taste of love that makes you crazy too.
もう君にキョン！私大暴走
Already Kyon for you! My big rampage,
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
isn't it magic that lets me be crazy with you?
だから君がキョンってなる恋になって
So fall into a love that makes you go Kyon,
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
here, have one, this is the taste of love.
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hehe, emang itu udah mulai gelap tapi...
Hehe, it is indeed starting to get dark, but...
Masih pada semangat nggak semuanya?!
Is everyone still feeling spirited?!
たくさんのゲストとパフォーマンスしてから、
After performing with many guests,
次は、コボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
next, Kobo would like to sing by herself again.
これから歌うこの曲は、最近コボが気に入っている曲で、
The song I'm about to sing is one Kobo has been liking recently.
聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
It made me feel happy when I listened to it.
皆さんも、この曲聴いて幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be glad if you all listen to this song and feel happy too.
それでは、次の曲。
And now, the next song.
青山テルマさんの、
By Thelma Aoyama...
「Happiness」です！
It's "Happiness"!
…思えるよ
...I can believe so.
何も言わなくても 感じてるよ
Even if we don't say anything, I feel it.
You're the one for me
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
You always make me happy
落ち込んで眠れなくて
Struggling to sleep when I'm down,
君との写真見つめている
I gaze at our photos.
いくつもの笑顔たちに
Saved by those many smiles,
助けられるよ my life
they keep me going, my life.
ずっと一緒だよ
We will be together forever.
泣いてもいいよ
It's okay to cry.
あの涙を抱きしめてくれた
You embraced those tears of mine.
どこにいるの？ ここにいるから
Where are you? I'm right here,
すぐに会いたくて
wanting to see you right away.
きっと Happiness
Surely Happiness,
君がいれば 大丈夫だって思えるよ
if you're here, I feel it'll be alright.
何も言わなくても 感じてるよ
Even if we don't say anything, I can feel it.
You're the one for me
君と Happiness
Happiness with you,
どんなときも ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ保存
I believe I'm never alone, no matter when.
涙溢れたって 歩けるね
Even if tears overflow, we can keep walking, right?
Please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Ever since I met you,
素直に笑っていられるよ
I can smile honestly.
少しずつ自分のこと
Little by little, I've come to...
好きになった for your love
like myself, for your love.
そう今なら ねえ心から
Yes, if it's now, hey, from my heart,
分かり合えるって思えるよ
I feel like we can understand each other.
強がらずに
Without pretending to be strong,
ありのままで
just as I am,
見つめてくれた
you looked at me.
だから Happiness
That's why Happiness,
君のことは 今よりももっと知りたくて
I want to know more about you than I do now.
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words,
大切な You're the one for me保存
you're my precious one, you're the one for me.
私も君に何か
I also want to do
できることしたいよ
something for you.
いつでも一緒だから
Since we're always together,
守っているから
I'll protect you,
ずっと
forever.
きっと Happiness 君がいれば
Surely Happiness, if you're here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I can believe that it'll be alright.
何も言わなくても
Even if we don't say anything,
感じてる You're the one for me
I feel it, you're the one for me.
君と Happiness保存
Happiness with you,
どんなときも ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe I'm never alone, no matter when.
涙溢れたって 歩けるね
Even if tears overflow, we can keep walking, right?
Please stay by my side
大切な You're the one for me
You're my precious one, you're the one for me.
いっくよー！
Here we go!
Oh, oh, oh, oh...保存
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
You always make me happy
Smile for me, baby
Ah-ah-ah-ah...
You always make me happy
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
Smile for me, baby
You always make me happy
ようこそお越しなさったご主人様
Welcome, my master.
隣に座ってせーの
Sit next to me, and on three...
萌え 萌え 萌え 萌え
Moe, moe, moe, moe!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be pleased with something like this?
ねぇ教えて 笑顔でアップップ
Hey, tell me, with a puffy smiling face.
一生そうやってご苦労様
Thanks for your hard work doing that for life.
私とあなたでせーの
You and me, and on three...
Love Love Love Love
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be pleased with something like this?
ねぇ教えて 笑顔でアップップ
Hey, tell me, with a puffy smiling face.
ひらりひらり 女の子
Fluttering, fluttering, a girl...
ふわりふわり 言葉の嘘
softly, softly, lying words...
それってつまり おさめなきゃ
In other words, I have to suppress...
感情的である 笑顔でアップップ
my emotional side, with a puffy smiling face.
人は見かけによらぬもの
People are not what they seem,
嘘 嘘だと見抜けない
you can't see through the lies, the lies.
したたかな袖 そそのかわ
With calculating sleeves and seductive skin...
鳥肌 鮫肌 アップップ
Goosebumps, gooseflesh, puff-puff!
待ちかねたご主人様
Long-awaited master,
いただきます
thank you for the meal.
私とあなたでせーの
You and me, and on three...
Love Love Love Love
これはお派手にご苦労様
Thanks for your hard work in such a flashy way.
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, with a puffy smiling face.
ひらりひらり ここはどこ
Fluttering, fluttering, where is this?
ふわりふわり 外はみぞれ
Softly, softly, it's sleeting outside...
それってつまり おさめなきゃ
In other words, I have to suppress...
感情的である 笑顔でアップップ
my emotional side, with a puffy smiling face.
歌いだす 秘密の鐘
The secret bell starts to ring,
終わることのないこの世界
in this world that never ends.
悲しい子供は
Sad children...
空しい子供は
Empty children...
眠らせて
Put them to sleep.
おままごと 遊びましょう
Playing house, let's play,
笑顔でアップップ
with a puffy smiling face.
ひらりひらり 女の子
Fluttering, fluttering, a girl...
ふわりふわり 言葉の嘘
softly, softly, lying words...
それってつまり おさめなきゃ
In other words, I have to suppress...
感情的である 笑顔でアップップ
my emotional side, with a puffy smiling face.
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play, with a puffy smiling face!
アップップ
Puff-puff!
Let's dance with me SUNDAY NIGHT MAGIC
何回でもかける true magic
A true magic that can be cast over and over.
まだまだ今日は夢見心地
Today, I'm still feeling dreamy.
夜更かししても朝まで game
Even if we stay up late, we'll play until morning.
何度でも繰り返すから shake
We'll repeat it over and over, so shake!
明日が来るその時まで
Until the moment tomorrow comes,
ねぇ、僕とどうだい？
hey, what do you say about being with me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わりに 退屈そうだけどどうだろう
At the end of a gloomy week, you look bored,
誘っていいかな？
but can I invite you out?
Come on now Come on now Come on, why not?
こっち向いてる？こっち向いてる？
Are you looking this way? Are you looking this way?
あっち向いてホイなんて勝たなくて
You don't have to win at "look the other way."
君のことだもん もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ<
Because it's you, listen to me more properly.
Hey, Let's sleep から逆転
Hey, let's turn things around from sleeping!
昨日の夜より今日の方が可愛いでしょ
I'm cuter today than yesterday night, right?
居ても立っても居られない
I can't just stand still.
聞こえるゼロ時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight,
時間切れの先へ
beyond the time limit...
飛び出して 駆け出して
Jump out, run out!
まだまだ夜は終われない
The night can't end just yet.
こんな最高な日々が
If these wonderful days...
明日も続いてくなら ねぇ、君もどうだい？
could continue tomorrow, hey, how about you?
待ち望んでる君の理想の
Your ideal that you've been waiting for...
お姫様の席はどうしよう 狙っていいかな？
What should we do with the princess's seat? Can I aim for it?
Next chance, Let's dance, Hey, 今でしょ？
Next chance, Let's dance, Hey, now is the time, right?
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Everyone and their dog matching the song,
ステップなんか踏んでみてご機嫌そう
try taking some steps, you look so happy!
昨日の夜より今日がずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than yesterday night,
続けたい時には
when you want to keep going...
聞こえるゼロ時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight,
時間切れの先へ
beyond the time limit...
終わらない 止まらない
It won't end, it won't stop!
まだまだ夜は長いから
Because the night is still long,
こんな最高な日々が
these wonderful days...
リズムに体を預けてみたら ほら 魔法みたい
If you try surrendering your body to the rhythm, look, it's like magic!
騒がしくてバカらしいような フライハイする毎日がいい
A noisy, silly, fly-high kind of everyday life is great!
魔法なんてありえない でも今夜だけは現実になるかも
Magic is impossible, but maybe just for tonight it will become real
体揺らして
Sway your body,
音に乗っかって
ride the sound,
踊れ君も
you dance too!
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法
In this endless night, a very special magic
君にもかけてあげるから
Because I'll cast it on you, too
僕の手をとってよ
Take my hand!
着替えるなら 鳴り止まないミュージック
If you're changing, to the non-stop music,
魔法が解けるまで 最高で最強な夜が
until the magic wears off, the best and strongest night...
今日も更けていく
...continues to deepen today
こんな夢みたいな日々が 明日も続いていくなら
If these dream-like days continue into tomorrow,
ねえ 君はどうする？
hey, what will you do?
アンコール 大胆に夜を飾るソング
Encore! A song that boldly decorates the night
何回でもかける超魔術
No matter how many times, I'll cast my super magic
まだまだ続くよ夢心地
This dreamlike state will go on and on
嘘みたいだけど 朝が来るその時まで
It seems like a lie, but until the morning comes,
ねえ 僕と踊ろう
hey, dance with me!
わー！やった、勝った勝った！やった！
Yay! We did it, we won! Yay!
え？なんか雲美味しそうじゃね？
Eh? Doesn't that cloud look delicious?
食べてみない？
Wanna try eating it?
ん、超美味しい！
Wow, it's super delicious!
美味しい！
Delicious!
おいちー！
Yummy!
何がしてるの？！
What are you doing?!
あ、食べられた！食べられた！やばいやばい！
Ah, we were caught! We were caught! Oh no, oh no!
はじめは食べてないです！
Hajime didn't eat it!
私の雲！
My cloud!
誰が！
Who did it?!
はじめは食べてない！食べてない！
Hajime didn't eat it! I didn't eat it!
こぼちゃんのだよ！何言ってるの？
It's Kobo-chan's! What are you saying?
Welcome, Kobo! Today is your birthday!
誕生日！
My birthday!
ハッピーバースデー、こぼ！ハッピーバースデー！
Happy Birthday, Kobo! Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！うわー、嬉しい！
Thank you! Wow, I'm so happy!
えー、じゃあ、こぼ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
Then, I want you to sing and dance with Kobo-senpai!
歌って踊りたい！ダンス、ダンス、ダンス！
We want to sing and dance! Dance, dance, dance!
こぼの振り付け！
It's Kobo's choreography!
Wow! Very nice!
こぼの、こぼ先生と呼んでください
Please call me Kobo... Kobo-sensei!
こぼおっちゃーん！ガキだから！
Kobo-otchan! Because you're a brat!
じゃあ、勉強した？もちろん！
So, did you practice? Of course!
あいちゅとり、こぼちゃん先輩、これ、コレオグラフ？
Ice tray, Kobo-chan senpai, this... choreography?
コレオグラフね。じゃあ、いきましょう！
Choreography, yeah. Well then, let's go!
いきましょう！Let's go! いいね！
Let's go! Let's go! Nice!
おしゅしゅ乗っけ！おしゅしゅのっけ、オッケーオッケー。じゃあいきましょう。
Put sushi on top! Put sushi on top, okay okay. Let's go.
誰も居なくなった
Nobody is left
二人だけの街に
In the city of just the two of us
機械仕掛けの時計が
The mechanical clock
夜の訪れ知らせる
Announces the arrival of night
夕暗が空を
The dusk dyes the sky
ワイン色に染めて
In the color of wine
不慣れな二人を
Inviting the two of us, who are still inexperienced
舞台へと誘う
To the stage
Chasse 'n' Whisk 'n' Natural-Turn
貴方に魔法をあげる
I'll give you a magic
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前は honey mead
Its name is honey mead
蜜月 Un·Deux·Trois
Honeymoon Un-Deux-Trois
互いの指を絡めて
We intertwine our fingers
Swinging, swinging, swinging just song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dream
Chase and whisk and natural tour
あなたに魔法をかける
I'll cast a spell on you
Throw away and over sway
魅惑の密葉に身
Into the enchanting thick leaves, my body...
Miel, baiser, un, deux, trois
その唇を重ねて
Let our lips overlap
Swinging, swinging, swinging just song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
月明かりが街を
The moonlight illuminates...
黄金色に照らして
...the town in a golden color
幼い二人は
The two young ones...
つまずきながら踊る
...dance while stumbling
Miel, baiser, un, deux, trois
互いの指を絡めて
Intertwining our fingers
Swinging, swinging, swinging just song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dream
シャバダバ Miel, baiser, un, deux, trois
Shabadaba, miel, baiser, un, deux, trois
その唇を重ねて
Let our lips overlap
Swinging, swinging, swinging just song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
楽しかった！ / 楽しかった！
That was fun! / That was fun!
やったー！
We did it!
おお、すごい！ダンス上手、ダンス上手！
Oh, awesome! You're so good at dancing, so good!
Terima kasih! / ありがとう！
Thank you! / Thank you!
なんか、うー、soigné.
It's like, uh, soigné.
コボ先輩もsoigné！
Kobo-senpai is also soigné!
Yes, soigné. カナちゃんsoigné.
Yes, soigné. Kana-chan is soigné.
そう、そう、そう！
Yes, yes, yes!
めっちゃelegant、めっちゃelegant！
Very elegant, very elegant!
ありがとう！ / ありがとう！
Thank you! / Thank you!
難しかった？ / あ、ちょっとね。
Was it difficult? / Ah, a little bit.
大丈夫、イージー！簡単ですよ、簡単だよ！
No problem, it's easy! It's so easy, so easy!
楽しかったー。呼んでくれてありがとうね。
That was so much fun. Thank you for inviting us.
コボ先輩、呼んでくれてありがとう！
Kobo-senpai, thank you for inviting us!
ありがとう！Sama-sama！
Thank you! You're welcome!
一緒に踊ってくれてありがとう。
Thank you for dancing with me.
Terima kasih, ya. / Sama-sama.
Thank you. / You're welcome.
Sama-sama. / Sama-sama.
You're welcome. / You're welcome.
Sama-sama, sama-sama...
You're welcome, you're welcome...
Happy Birthday！ / Happy Birthday！
Happy Birthday! / Happy Birthday!
おめでとう！ / ファイト！
Congratulations! / Do your best!
ファイト！ファイト！
Do your best! Do your best!
じゃあ、バイバイ！ / バイバイ！
Well then, bye-bye! / Bye-bye!
みんな帰っちゃった...
Everyone has gone home...
さみしい...
I'm lonely...
かなしい...
I'm sad...
誰も来ないのかな...
I wonder if no one else is coming...
サヨナラの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
サヨナラの後は 忘れさせて
Make me forget after we say goodbye
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない
Won't leave me
話せない
Can't let go
戻りたい
I want to go back
Take me free...
この恋は君がいたあの日々
This love, those days when you were here...
止まった彩り...
The stopped colors...
部屋の中は香水だらけに染めた チュベローズのフレーバー
the room was stained with perfume, a tuberose flavor.
当たり前さえも奇跡 当たり障りない君との軌跡
Even the ordinary is a miracle, my harmless path with you.
どれだけ恋しくなっても 超えられない君を
No matter how much I yearn for you, I can't reach you.
今ならわかる気がして
Now I feel like I understand...
今から過去にも戻れるなら
If I could go back to the past starting now...
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Give me a kiss before goodbye.
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
Let me forget everything after goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave.
離せない
I won't let go.
戻りたい
I want to go back.
Take me free
呪いたい お互い知っているのよ 気づけばあなたのことばかり浮かべて
I want to hate you, we both know it... Before I knew it, only thoughts of you filled my mind.
明日になれば大丈夫
If tomorrow comes, I'll be fine.
何度言い聞かせればいいのだろう
How many times must I convince myself?
愛という沼に溺れてる
I'm drowning in the swamp called love.
私の声は届かない？
Will my voice not reach you?
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Give me a kiss before goodbye.
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
Let me forget everything after goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave.
離せない
I won't let go.
戻りたい
I want to go back.
Take me free
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Give me a kiss before goodbye.
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
Let me forget everything after goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave.
離さない
I won't let go.
戻れない
I can't go back.
Take me free
帰れない日々 抱きしめたまま
Holding onto the days I cannot return to,
いつかそう いつか...
someday, yes, someday...
弱い心が捕まる前に
Before my weak heart gets caught,
そっとあなたを遠ざけた
I quietly pushed you away.
あぁ こんな気持ち
Ah, this kind of feeling...
辛すぎるよ もう
is just too painful already.
あなたは誰なの
Who are you?
どこに隠れてたの
Where were you hiding?
酷く怯えてる
I'm terribly frightened,
うつむいたままの
with my head kept down.
見上げるな
Don't look up,
私が待ってた
I was waiting.
またあの季節
Again that season comes,
夜空は白く
the night sky turns white,
あなたもいて
and you are there too.
触れてこないで
Don't touch me,
嬉しいけれど
even though I'm happy,
心が痛い
my heart aches.
離したくない
I don't want to let go,
離れたくない
I don't want to leave,
でも諦めてた
but I had given up.
もうこれ以上 好きになれない
I can't love you any more than this,
失う痛み 耐え切れないよ保存
I can't bear the pain of losing you.
帰れない日々 抱きしめたまま保存
Holding onto the days I cannot return to,
いつかそう いつか...
someday, yes, someday...
ただそばにいて
Just stay by my side,
それだけでいい
that's all I need,
素直にはなれないけれど
even though I can't be honest with myself.
さあ 顔を上げて
Come on, raise your head
歩み始めなきゃ
You have to start walking
リアルな私よ
Real me...
気付いて
...notice it
また あの季節 この空の下
Under this sky once again in that season...
見上げている
...I am looking up
傷付いたもの もう元には
The broken things won't return...
戻らないけど定義
...to the way they were, but...
離したくない
I don't want to let go
離れたくない
I don't want to leave
もう諦めない
I won't give up anymore
あなたの心 傷付けてでも
Even if I hurt your heart...
この気持ち 嘘はつけない
...I can't lie about this feeling
いつか笑顔で 話せるような
Someday, looking for a me...
私を見つけて
...who can talk with a smile
ただそばにいて 聞かせてほしい
Just stay by my side, I want to hear...
二度と一人には しないと
...that you'll never leave me alone again
帰らない日々 抱きしめたまま
Holding on to the days that will never return
きっと そう きっと
Surely, yes, surely
あの日の気持ち 受け止めないと
If I don't accept the feelings of that day...
前に進むことができない
...I can't move forward
離したくない
I don't want to let go
離れたくない
I don't want to leave
一つの願いは
My only wish...
大好きだよと 伝えたいだけ
...is that I just want to tell you that I love you
本当 素直じゃないけれど
Although I'm not really honest
So... How is it, guys?
Mmm, that was Closing.
Did you take a lot of screenshots? Ooh!
And, ah, how about my new stage?
Woah!
It's very cloudy here.
Yeah, as you can see, there's two big pictures on the left and right.
Mmm, so cute, right? みんなどうだった？ こぼのパフォーマンス！
Mmm, so cute, right? How was Kobo's performance, everyone?
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？
I wonder if you got a lot of screenshots?
こぼの新しいステージはもうどうだった？可愛いでしょ？
How was Kobo's new stage? Cute, right?
Big picturesがありますので、めちゃ可愛いよね？
Since there are big pictures, it's super cute, right?
Mmm, so, actually...
Yeah, we're already at the end of the show, guys, but...
そろそろお別れの時間になりますよ。
...it is almost time for us to part.
But don't worry, mmm...
But don't worry...
Kobo still has something to share with you guys. まだ皆さんにお知らせがあります！
Kobo still has an announcement to share with you guys!
じゃん！ じゃじゃーん！
Tada! Ta-da!
Wee! Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
Yay! Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
This time, Kobo's birthday merch theme is Jellyfish Princess...
Princess!
I wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time,
and finally, my wish came true! So,
how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the key visual is drawn by Scotti-sensei. Mm.
Scotti-sensei, arigatou! Arigatou!
Thank you, Scotti-sensei! Thank you!
And... as you wish, guys.
Finally, ta-da!
Kobokers' happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers and perfect for cheering me during events.
Keren banget...
It's so cool!
happi, happi, happi. Come on, buy happi, happi!
And if you look closely, this happi design is like...
my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's Chillers in the front,
and me...
in the back, right?
And... next...
we have this "Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" tapestry!
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face every morning.
And also, don't forget to praise the Lord everyday!
Then, look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this" button badge set!
Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit,
and the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself. It looks good, right?
Do you like it? I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag,
or your hat, or your... heart.
Okay, so this one is one of my favorites.
One, two, three...
Ta-da! The plushie keychain!
It's me! But mini Kobo in mini form!
You can bring me anywhere: on your backpack,
your keys, your...
motorcycle,
car, whatever, even next to your computer
while you watch my streams!
So soft and squishy!
And finally,
we also have the situational voice pack!
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
What does it mean?
Buy it!
Buy it, okay? So you know what does it mean.
Yippee! It's a special voice pack where I talk to you
about Jellyfish Princess
and, you know, your one and only just for you.
Yeah, don't miss out on my birthday merch, guys.
If you buy the set, you'll get a special bromide
If you buy the set, you'll get a special bromide card
with my signature on it!
The merch is available for a limited time only,
so you can grab yours
from the official shop. Links are in the description.
So, yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo's performance today.
以上、コボコのお知らせでした！
And that's all for Koboko's announcements!
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので、
Since the links are posted in the description and chat section,
クリックしてね！ Oh yeah!
please click them! Oh yeah!
But...
I can hear some of you want an encore.
アンコール？アンコール、アンコールほしい？
An encore? Do you guys want an encore, an encore?
じゃあ、しょうがないわ。
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Please listen...
...Sweet Memories.
「Sweet Memories」
[Song Title: Sweet Memories]
Sweet Memories
（Lyrics: 松本隆 / Music: 大村雅朗）
[Song: Sweet Memories]
[Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto / Music: Masaaki Omura]
なつかしい痛みだわ
A nostalgic pain,
ずっと前に忘れていた
I had forgotten long ago.
でもあなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたの
time only went backwards.
「幸福？」と聞かないで
Don't ask, "Are you happy?"
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not good at telling lies.
友だちならいるけど
I have friends, but...
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
I couldn't burn like that.
失った夢だけが
Why is it that only the dreams I lost
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った優しさも今は
Even the gentleness that passed by is now
甘い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
just a sweet memory, SWEET MEMORIES.
Don't kiss me baby we can never be
So don't add more pain Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights Thinking of you...
...longing for your touch I have once loved you so much
...longing for your touch, I once loved you so much.
あの頃は若すぎて
Back then we were too young,
悪戯に傷つけあった二人
hurting each other in mischief.
色褪せた哀しみも今は
The faded sadness is now
遠い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
a distant memory, SWEET MEMORIES.
La la la...
失った夢だけが
Why is it that only the dreams I lost
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った優しさも今は
Even the gentleness that passed by is now
甘い記憶 SWEET MEMORIES
just a sweet memory, SWEET MEMORIES.
フィナーレ。
（Lyrics: eill / Music: eill, Ryo LEFTY Miyata）
[Song: Finale]
[Lyrics: eill / Music: eill, Ryo LEFTY Miyata]
君はほんとに わかってないよ
You really don't get it.
例えばハッピー
For example, rather than a happy...
エンドより
...ending,
甘くて豪華なデザートより
rather than a sweet and luxurious dessert,
君がいいんだよ
I'd rather have you.
ふたつの傘より
Rather than two umbrellas,
相合傘
sharing one umbrella.
ちょっと冷たいけど
Though it's a bit cold,
愛するための代償なら
if it's the price to pay for love,
いくらでもどうぞ
take as much as you'd like.
ただずっとそばにいたい
I just want to be by your side forever.
ねぇダーリン
Hey darling,
星屑もない
even without stardust,
ふたりぼっちの世界でずっと
in our world of just the two of us, forever.
最後の花火を上げて
Let's set off the final fireworks,
フィナーレを飾って
decorating the finale.
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Falling into a love where miracles fall,
ダーリンもう離さないで
Darling, don't ever let go.
味気ない世界も悪くないね
Even a dull world isn't so bad.
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I fall in love,
出会えないよきっと
I'll surely never find another like you.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness.
いつか今日を忘れても
Even if we forget today someday,
君がいいんだよ
I'd still choose you.
全部分け合って初めて通じ合えた
By sharing everything, we finally understood each other.
ずっと覚えているよ
I will remember this forever.
ねぇダーリン 星屑もない
Hey darling, even without stardust,
ふたりぼっちの世界でずっと
in our world of just the two of us, forever.
最後の花火を上げて
Let's set off the final fireworks,
フィナーレを誓って
swearing our finale.
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Falling into a love where miracles fall,
ダーリンもう離さないで
Darling, don't ever let go.
素っ気ない世界も悪くないね
Even an indifferent world isn't so bad.
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I fall in love,
忘れられないよきっと
I will surely never be able to forget you.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness.
味気ないね
It's dull, isn't it?
でもそれがね
But that is...
ふたりの幸せ
...our happiness.
Oh my god, I almost cried. I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys! Thank you for today. Thank you, thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zetai's vickice she covered this finale song first, and then I was inspired. So yeah.
Aku balikin ke sini, hehehe.
I'll return it to here, hehehe.
イヤ、イヤ。今日は来てくれて、今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございました！
Yeah, yeah. Thank you so much for coming today, and for watching until the very end!
I hope you guys enjoy all the performance.
I hope you guys enjoy all the performances.
Um, yeah. This whole stream!
みんな大好き！Thank you for your birthday wishes!
I love you all! Thank you for your birthday wishes!
後で読んであげますね。うん。
I'll read them later. Yep.
バイバイ、みんな！No more encore, no more encore. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, everyone! No more encore, no more encore. Bye-bye!
Boko boko boko! Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Hehehe! Bye-bye!
Yeah!
Thank you! I can't be as bright as now without you! - Kobo